it’s hard to be a normal person
that’s just not me
I’m writing a journal
to keep my feelings hiding
across the bridge what will I see
I wanna see it
dreaming my dreams
miracles, beautiful
here we go all the way
running from my life ends now
use to keep holding back my thoughts
would be wrong if you’re gone
found my way through the stars
if I could reach to your heart
money still can’t buy me love
but there’s still life when there’s
hope around
like a rainbow in the clouds
a gift from above
kiss me before sunrise
or I’m leaving you tonight
my love found a place
to stay and rest like bed
always and forever
meant to be together
if we could change this world today with you